The hedgehog has 4 small legs with small claws on the feet, a small nose, small ears and small eyes.
They don't look great but they feel scents great.
That way they chase up what they want to eat.
But what does the hedgehog eat
Well, the hedgehog eats worms, beetles, snails, bird eggs they can take, small mouse cubs, frogs ...
... and even snakes they can eat.
The hedgehog can handle pretty good snake poison, so they can.
What is most amazing about the hedgehog eats beetles, do you know what it is
Well, because what you eat comes out like poop.
So when the hedgehogs poop, it is pooping glitter.
The hedgehog's poop shines off the beetle shells that are in it.
You can hear how they scream around there at night because these are awake at night.
Then they crawl out and look for food in our gardens
You can actually feed the hedgehog if you want.
You should keep in mind not to feed it with milk because they are allergic, instead you can exhibit water ...
... or cat food they can enjoy.
The hedgehog is starting to wake up now in the spring for all winter it has been in hibernation.
It hides in a pile of leaves or twigs and it is almost like dead.
The heart beats only a few blows and it just breathes a little neighbor.
But then in the spring it arrives.
In fact, the hedgehogs are not very common anymore.
They will actually be included in the red list that will be this year.
This means that they are starting to become really unusual.
You do not know exactly why the hedgehogs are getting fewer, but they have difficulty finding good places to sleep.
If you have a garden, it is good to leave some deciduous piles and rice piles where the hedgehog can winter.
But now I think we should have our own hedgehogs.
So, now I've got some help.
-Yes!
We are going to make hedgehogs.
We will make the hedgehogs of witch dough and then we need flour, salt, water ...
And a little like that.
Then we want the magic dough to be brown, or how
For the hedgehog is brown.
Then we have old coffee grounds that I was going to color with.
And to tags, what do we have then
What is that for something then
Ehm, conifer.
Yes, it is.
We have pine cones if we are to make small tags.
Let's go
Now we are going to make magic dough pink.
Then we will have 1 cup flour.
Should you pour in
It's like I'm baking.
Yes, but just like when we bake.
So we should have in salt, half a deciliter.
So.
Then we will have in a little coffee sump, what remains when you have made coffee.
If we get a little.
So, half a deciliter.
Yes, take everything together.
So we should have some water, half a deciliter.
So.
I want to do.
-Yes you should do as you please.
Should we build a small nest to the hedgehog
Look here you'll see.
Here we have some paper.
Here the hedgehog will be allowed to live.
Idgehogs like to rest in winter and go to hibernation.
The heart beats very dealing, almost so they lie dead in deciduous piles.
So I thought we were taking some old leaves.
I usually glue like a small V, or one up and down V.
So we attach some leaves here.
Look